A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files, 1967-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files 1967-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
For ten years from the date of creation, access to these records will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia -2.1-340 ff.) or with the specific permission of the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1988 Aug 24.
Contents List
- Conflict of Interest 1984 Jan - 1985 July, 1 of 3 (Box 1)
- Conflict of Interest 1983 Jan - Dec, 2 of 3 (Box 1)
- Conflict of Interest 1981 Dec - 1982 Dec, 3 of 3 (Box 1)
- Equal Opportunity Programs 1974-1975; 1979-1981 (Box 1)
- Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1970-1984 (Box 1)
- Gifts and Grants 1970-1984 (Box 1)
- Library, Alderman 1968-1984 (Box 2)
- Personnel Administration 1974-1984 (Box 2)
- "Administration of the University of Virginia at the Senior Level" 1967 May (Box 2)
- White Burkett Miller Council 1981, 1 of 2 (Box 2)
- White Burkett Miller Council 1979-1980, 2 of 2 (Box 2)
- White Burkett Miller Council 1983, 1 of 2 (Box 3)
- White Burkett Miller Council 1982, 2 of 2 (Box 3)